[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "I was amazed ………………… his brilliance",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "with"
      },
      {
        "2": "at"
      },
      {
        "3": "by"
      },
      {
        "4": "to"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "at"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "He is afflicted ………………… a serious illness.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "with"
      },
      {
        "2": "to"
      },
      {
        "3": "by"
      },
      {
        "4": "of"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "She does not agree ……………… me.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "upon"
      },
      {
        "2": "to"
      },
      {
        "3": "with"
      },
      {
        "4": "None of these"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "You must apologize ……………… him for your rude behaviour.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "to"
      },
      {
        "2": "by"
      },
      {
        "3": "with"
      },
      {
        "4": "for"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "Is it possible to achieve just about everything one aims ………………?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "of"
      },
      {
        "2": "by"
      },
      {
        "3": "for"
      },
      {
        "4": "to"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "She often boasts ……………… her aristocratic upbringing.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "on"
      },
      {
        "2": "about"
      },
      {
        "3": "for"
      },
      {
        "4": "by"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "about"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "Don’t brood ………………… your mistakes and failures.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "at"
      },
      {
        "2": "with"
      },
      {
        "3": "by"
      },
      {
        "4": "over"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "over"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "We decided to call ……………… the principal.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "at"
      },
      {
        "2": "on"
      },
      {
        "3": "for"
      },
      {
        "4": "to"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "He has been charged ……………… the murder of his neighbor.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "for"
      },
      {
        "2": "by"
      },
      {
        "3": "with"
      },
      {
        "4": "to"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "After the dance competition, the judges were comparing their judgement scores ……………… each other.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "to"
      },
      {
        "2": "for"
      },
      {
        "3": "with"
      },
      {
        "4": "by"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "with"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "We went out ……………… the rain.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "however"
      },
      {
        "2": "because of"
      },
      {
        "3": "in spite of"
      },
      {
        "4": "instead of"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "in spite of"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "moduleId": 2,
    "question": "The wind ……………… furiously.",
    "choices": [
      {
        "1": "blew"
      },
      {
        "2": "blown"
      },
      {
        "3": "blowned"
      },
      {
        "4": "blewed"
      }
    ],
    "answer": "blew"
  }
]